Contact

carriern9@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/carrie-blair-bsn-rn-16668390 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

BLS

EMR

Epic Systems

Carrie Blair BSN, RN

Nurse Manager

Houston, Texas Area

Summary

Accomplished nursing leader with 27 years of combined experience contributing to the continuous delivery of top quality patient care in compliance with policies, procedures, and regulations of State Boards of Nursing. Equipped with a strong background of 10 years critical care followed by 17 years of ambulatory care, driving the development and efforts of talented teams of nursing and allied health professionals. Highly committed to the compassionate care of patients and family members, providing individuals with the support and education to optimize wellness and comfort. Close monitoring of patient outcomes, as well as physician productivity.

Experience

Kelsey-Seybold Clinic
Nurse Manager
May 2003 - Present (17 years 3 months)
The Woodlands and Woodlands ObGyn Clinic

American Mobile Healthcare
Traveling Nurse
August 2001 - May 2003 (1 year 10 months)
Houston, Texas

Emergency Department / Critical Care Nurse

Charleston Area Medical Center Health System Charge Nurse Clinical IV June 1993 - December 2001 (8 years 7 months) Charleston, West Virginia

Level I Trauma and Stroke Emergency Department

Education

Thiel College

Bachelor's Degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (1989 - 1993)